Thank you for watching!
9 wins IM
Am or Am-kun
July 31
Gifu Prefecture
Type A
Right-handed
One brother
Yes, I'm in second place.
My charm points are my long eyelashes and
And...
My motto is
“Never choose the brush of the workshop
Let's see...
Easy
My favorite saying is
Ahhh!
Ah!
ESTP
Hobby is basketball
Special skill is cooking eggs
On my daughter's day, I play games with Haruma
My favorite colors are red, purple and yellow.
My favorite seasons are autumn and spring.
Favorite artist is Nishi-san
Favorite comedian: Eiko Kanoh
Favorite TV show?
Let's see... what is it?
Hapling, Hapling, Hapling.
Favorite movie? I like animated movies.
Favorite YouTube?
YouTube. Eiko Shikano's YouTube.
Favorite TikToker I don't really have a favorite TikToker.
Favorite character is...
Goku from Dragon Ball
My favorite anime is
Her, Kanokari and later, The Bride of the Fifth Estate.
My favorite food is meat. Favorite food is meat
Parsley
Mmmm...calpis
Favorite candy?
I don't eat much.
Chocolate, chocolate bars.
Strawberries, melons, watermelons...
Favorite animal is a dog.
Cats.
Favorite place, my hometown
Favorite emoji, tsk, the one with the smiley face.
Favorite sport is basketball.
Favorite number 7
My favorite dish is eggs.
My favorite subjects are physical education and Japanese.
Math, Science, Social Studies
Dentist
Karaoke box
Songs by NISSY
This entertainment by NISSY
I think it's great that you offer how to tell your fans how good you are.
I think it's really good that you are offering how to convey the fun of entertainment to your fans!
I think it's cool!
My favorite NISSY songs are Do Do and Don't Let Me Go!
The CD you gave me is Super Dragon's first album.
This is Mr. Nissy.
It's Mr. Nissy!
I'm packing NISSY's goods.
NISSY's album
I think I'm a singer now.
I'd like to play the piano or guitar.
I'm an indoor person.
Hokkaido
Singing and playing games
Maybe not. Maybe.
I'll talk to someone.
I guess my favorite hairstyle is NCT's hair arrangement.
I like the all-back bun.
I'd like to try perming my hair.
For makeup, I'd like to try Dewall's foundation concealer.
Hmmm...
If people around me are excited...
Average hours of sleep
Heh, but 10 hours or more than 10 hours.
I always turn on the humidifier.
What was your previous life?
A monkey.
I like to think I've been a human being.
Sweet.
What do you eat?
tuna, mayo, salmon, bonito, radish, egg, konnyaku
radish, egg, konnyaku
mmm tuna
mmm corn
Mmm corn
Various
Mr. West
The future
Is it the happiest thing you've ever done?
Being accepted for an audition.
Let's see...
When talent
I can rely on you
Always having fun
Leader
Younger sister
Ummm...
Younger sister.
Mmm, big brother
He's a good singer.
You have a high voice.
What is your favorite song in Love Ann? What is your favorite song on Labuan?
Hmmm...
Now or Never
Glory Days
I want to go to a theme park. Amusement park
AAA
Mr. AAA?
Hmm...
I really want to play some cool music.
I want to play cool music.
As for the male members, except for the current show, the three of us are playing a game.
A game called APEX.
I wonder who it is.
Haruma?
He's kind and reliable.
Heh?
Oh, you want to talk about the funniest thing I've heard recently?
I'm happy when I talk to Isshin.
I'll become Isshin Ai haare and go wild.
I want to go wild.
I'll raise the tension myself.
Information I haven't told anyone.
Yes...
I like rock music.
Yeah.
Let's definitely go to Tokyo Dome.
As for Love One, I'd love to go on a dome tour or a world tour.
I'd love to go on a world tour.
Thanks for watching.